After searching through the night for your shattered peace.
After throwing your dawn-lit sorrow into the world.
You'll look for my friendly shoulder,
my embrace, your shelter.
You'll scream my name pointlessly in an empty room.
After having my love for nearly a lifetime.
After throwing away a love so true.
It has been a long time since I left.
You used to scream, "I dare you!"
And now you hear my curse whispering in your ear.
You are going to regret treating me like this.
You will spend sleepless nights on an endless pursuit.
And every drink you have will remind you of me.
It has been a while since I left.
You used to scream, "I dare you."
And now you hear my curse whispering in your ear.
You are going to regret treating me like this.
You will spend sleepless nights on an endless search.
And every drink you have will remind you of me.
Thank you. Thank you.
My name is Tim Bernardes.
I'm from São Paulo, Brazil, singer-songwriter.
It's so cool to be here.
I love the show. I have been watching this, it's crazy, and thank you for being here.
Thank you. Any Brazilians? Any Brazilians here?
There's always Brazilians, I love that.
Good morning. Good afternoon. Good evening.
So you know that? Last year I was invited to do the Tiny Desk Brasil. That was an edition that happened in São Paulo, my town.
And I was just rehearsing a show with orchestra.
We managed to put a bunch of orchestral players and now I wanted to do the opposite.
The stripped-down that is actually my favorite way of playing, like, the solo thing.
So you can really focus on songwriting, not all this stuff.
And I'm gonna play some stuff I didn't play there and that I don't play often, so now I'm gonna play a song that I've never played live.
That I'd done with BADBADNOTGOOD and the maestro Arthur Verocai from Brazil.
It's a song called "Poeira Cósmica."
Night has fallen, there's a new moon over South America.
A sign from the sky.
Are we or are we not cosmic dust?
Feel it in the wind, stardust.
Time, all at once, there is more than what meets the eye in this life.
I don't want to think anymore, I don't want to understand.
Wherever I go, I feel without knowing.
Unconsciously, I know there's some kind of mystery.
And you've felt it, too, in the infinity of the soul.
Something more.
That we are not just cosmic dust.
Thank you.
I'll sing a song now from my latest album that is called Mil Coisas Invisíveis.
It's a song that I wrote originally for Gal Costa, my great hero from Brazil.
And she recorded this song and I recorded it on my own album.
And I'm preparing a new album for next year, but I'm gonna play this one from the old album.
All beauty, all love,
is beautiful, it's truly beautiful.
Go away, sadness, please, be on your way,
I want to see myself smiling.
Something new has arrived, arrived, arrived.
The longing has already gone away.
Farewell, I already know who I am.
Farewell, I'm already on my way.
Maybe I won't come back.
Maybe I'm already arriving.
From afar to calm myself down.
Up close, everything feels so big.
It's beautiful, it's amazing to be here.
The world is massive.
All beauty, all love.
It's beautiful. It's really beautiful.
Go away, sadness, please.
Move along. I want to see myself smiling.
Something new has arrived, arrived, arrived.
The longing is already gone.
Goodbye. I already know who I am.
Goodbye. I'm already on my way.
Maybe I won't come back.
Maybe I'm already arriving.
From afar to calm myself down.
Up close everything feels so big.
It's beautiful and amazing to be here.
The world is massive.
All beauty, all love, is beautiful, it's truly beautiful.
Go away, sadness, please.
Go on, I want to see myself smiling.
It's beautiful, it's truly beautiful.
It's beautiful, truly beautiful.
Thank you very much.
Thank you very, very, very much.
Thank you so much for having me.
I'll play one last song, a song that I originally recorded with my dear band back in São Paulo, O Terno.
That I also have besides the solo project so it's a song called "Eu Vou."
I won't put up bad energy in my life anymore.
I will no longer carry the weight and burdens that aren't mine.
I'm going to run toward all those beautiful things that I long for.
I want to walk alongside those who, just like me, see the glass half full.
I'm going, I'm going, I'm going, I'm going, I'm going.
I came to this world to live.
I'm going to try living freer, lighter and unbound.
I'm going to celebrate life, death, time and dreams.
I go in peace. Everything ends and begins again, time is steady and moves forward.
I want more, for only through dreaming do we create and come away with something different.
I'm going, I'm going, I'm going, I'm going, I'm going.
I came into this world to live.
I'm going, I'm going, I'm going.
OK. Thank you. Kisses.